const level15Questions = [
 {
        question: "Gội đầu",
        answers: ["洗发 (xǐfà)", "洗脸 (xǐ liǎn)"],
        correct: "洗发 (xǐfà)",
    },
            {
        question: "Rau củ",
        answers: ["蔬菜 (shūcài)", "炒菜 (chǎo cài)"],
        correct: "蔬菜 (shūcài)",
    },
            {
        question: "Bia",
        answers: ["酒 (jiǔ)", "啤酒 (píjiǔ)"],
        correct: "啤酒 (píjiǔ)",
    },
            {
        question: "Hài lòng",
        answers: ["满溢 (mǎnyì)", "满意 (mǎnyì)"],
        correct: "满意 (mǎnyì)",
    },
            {
        question: "Văn phòng",
        answers: ["办公室 (bàngōngshì)", "公司 (gōngsī)"],
        correct: "办公室 (bàngōngshì)",
    },
            {
        question: "Báo cáo",
        answers: ["报告 (bàogào)", "包子 (bāozi)"],
        correct: "报告 (bàogào)",
    },
            {
        question: "Sổ tay, máy tính xách tay (laptop)",
        answers: ["笔记本 (bǐjìběn)电脑(diànnǎo)", "圆珠笔 (yuánzhūbǐ)"],
        correct: "笔记本 (bǐjìběn)电脑(diànnǎo)",
    },
            {
        question: "Báo cáo tuần",
        answers: ["周报 (zhōubào)", "周末 (zhōumò)"],
        correct: "周报 (zhōubào)",
    },
            {
        question: "Thăm bạn bè",
        answers: ["看朋友 (kàn péngyǒu)", "看报 (kànbào)"],
        correct: "看朋友 (kàn péngyǒu)",
    },
            {
        question: "Đi làm",
        answers: ["上班 (shàngbān)", "上课 (shàngkè)"],
        correct: "上班 (shàngbān)",
    },
            {
        question: "Tan học",
        answers: ["下班 (xiàbān)", "下课 (xiàkè)"],
        correct: "下课 (xiàkè)",
    },
            {
        question: "Ông chủ",
        answers: ["老板 (lǎobǎn)", "老伴 (lǎobàn)"],
        correct: "老板 (lǎobǎn)",
    },
            {
        question: "Tài liệu",
        answers: ["文件 (wénjiàn)", "课文 (kèwén)"],
        correct: "文件 (wénjiàn)",
    },
                {
        question: "Giá cả",
        answers: ["价格 (jiàgé)", "讨价还价 (tǎojià huánjià)"],
        correct: "价格 (jiàgé)",
    },
                {
        question: "Đồng nghiệp",
        answers: ["同事 (tóngshì)", "同桌 (tóngzhuō)"],
        correct: "同事 (tóngshì)",
    },
                {
        question: "Khách hàng",
        answers: ["客户 (kèhù)", "客气 (kèqi)"],
        correct: "客户 (kèhù)",
    },
                {
        question: "Đầu tư",
        answers: ["投资 (tóuzī)", "亏损 (kuīsǔn)"],
        correct: "投资 (tóuzī)",
    },
];

export default level15Questions;